( TRAIN APPROACHES )
( TRAIN HORN BLARES )
TANNOY : ' Due to a computer error ,
' the food stamp programme has been suspended until further notice .
' Please do not apply at this time .
' All applicants for work wages now report to window D.
' Thank you . '
Last place of employment ?
Denver , Colorado .
Worked there for ten years . Then things just seemed to dry up .
They lost 14 banks in one week .
So , can ...
There 's nothing available for you right now .
PREACHER : They use their tongues to deceive .
The venom of snakes is under their lips .
Their mouths are full of bitterness and curses .
And in their paths , nothing but ruin and misery .
And the fear of God is not before their eyes .
They have taken the hearts and minds of our leaders .
They have recruited the rich and the powerful ,
and they have blinded us to the truth .
Our human spirit is corrupted .
Why do we worship greed ?
Because outside the limit of our sight ,
feeding off us , perched on top of us from birth to death ,
are our owners !
Our owners !
They have us . They control us .
They are our masters .
Wake up ! They 're all about you , all around you .
TV : ' Sometimes when I watch TV , I stop being myself ,
' and I 'm a star of a series or I have my own talk show ,
' or I 'm on the news getting out of a limo , going someplace important .
' All I ever have to do is be famous .
' People watch me , and they love me .
' And I 'll never , never grow old ,
' and I 'll never die . '
Excuse me . You need anybody ?
- Maybe . - I 've got my own tools .
This is a union job .
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING , LAUGHING )
So ...
Er , then may I please speak with the shop steward ?
Sir ?
Hey , there 's no sleeping on this site ,
so you park your ass someplace else tonight .
Excuse me .
Then when do I get paid ?
Thursday .
You need a place to stay ?
Chesterfield 's over on 4th street . They 've got hot food and showers .
I 'm going that way if you want me to show you .
( CAR HORN )
I don 't like nobody following me unless I know why .
Well , I don 't turn up with anybody till I see where he 's going .
They 'll be serving the food up soon .
Good , I 'm starving .
Whoa !
Hey Frank , how 's it going ?
You may get a chance to meet some of the folk .
This here is Gilbert . Anything you need , he knows where to find it .
- Hi . - Hi .
- What you got in that pack ? Tools ? - Yes , sir .
If you can use them , we can use you .
The shower 's caving in over there .
Let 's get something to eat .
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING )
There you go !
Howdy !
- Peas ? - Yeah , plum .
- Some more ? - Yeah .
I 've got a wife and two kids back in Detroit .
I haven 't seen them in six months .
The steel mills were laying people off left and right .
They finally went under .
We gave the steel companies a break when they needed it .
Know what they gave themselves ?
Raises .
The golden rule .
" He who has the gold makes the rules . "
If they close one more factory ,
we should take a sledge to one of their fancy fucking foreign cars .
You know , you ought to have a little more patience .
Yeah , well , I 'm all out .
The whole deal 's like some kind of crazy game .
They put you at the starting line ,
the name of the game is , " Make it through life . "
Only everyone is out for themselves and looking to do you in at the same time .
Okay , man , here we are .
Here we are . Now , you do what you can ,
but remember , I 'm going to do my best to blow your ass away .
So , how are you going to make it ?
I deliver a hard day 's work for my money , I just want a chance . It 'll come .
I believe in America . I follow the rules .
Everybody has got their own hard times these days .
( HARMONICA PLAYS )
TV : ' And you 've always thought you couldn 't wear press-on nails
' because of all the active things you do ?
' Well , if you 're ready for beautiful , natural-looking , easy-to-apply nails ,
recoloured in seven luscious hues ,
' just ... '
' Our impulses are being redirected .
' We are living in an artificially-induced state of consciousness
' that resembles sleep . '
Goddamn hacker . That 's the second time tonight that asshole has cut in .
' The movement was begun eight months ago
' by a small group of scientists who discovered ... quite by accident ...
' These signals being sent through ... '
- That thing 's giving me a headache . - Yeah , tell me about it .
Must have took the hacker months to figure out how to do this .
' The poor and the under-class are growing .
' Racial justice and human rights are non-existent .
' They have created a repressive society ,
' and we are their unwitting accomplices .
' Their intention to rule rests with the annihilation of consciousness .
' We have been lulled into a trance .
' They have made us indifferent to ourselves , to others .
' We are focused only on our own gain .
' We ...
' Please understand ,
' they are safe as long as they are not discovered .
' That is their primary method of survival .
' Keep us asleep , keep us selfish , keep us sedated . '
Blow it out of your ass !
( INDISTINCT )
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING )
Choir practice went a little late last night , didn 't it ?
The church lets us use their kitchen .
Till four in the morning ?
( CHUCKLES ) Hey , we take care of a lot of people here .
' They are dismantling the sleeping middle-class .
' More and more people are becoming poor .
' We are their cattle .
' We are being bred for slavery . '
- Not again ! - ' We cannot break their signal .
' Our transmitter is not powerful enough .
' The signal must be shut off at the source . We have ... '
- Billy , I have a headache . - Me too , honey .
Could somebody please explain to me what the hell all that 's about ?
Just that idiot licking his nuts again .
( GOSPEL CHOIR SINGING )
GILBERT : And there 's nothing wrong with it .
We have to face facts . Only a few seconds got on the air .
It 's time to forget about breaking in on top of their signal .
They 're only gonna jam us out again and again .
Then we have to send the shipment out on the street .
No , no , no ... it 's not gonna work that way . We 've been all through this !
We have no other choice .
( CLATTERING )
Robbing banks .
Manufacturing Hoffman lenses till we 're blue in the face .
We 're just not gonna reach enough people !
We gotta find new people , strong people who 'll work with us .
That 's my baby .
Oh !
Just leaving , you know ... Your door was open .
Just wanted to close it . Didn 't want no one breaking in .
- Neighbourhood watch . - Yeah ...
Now let me touch your face .
- That 's fine . - Mm-hmm , good . Now your hands .
- That 's fine . - Good .
- You 're a working man . - Yes , sir .
Here . It 's the revolution . Let me show you .
I gotta be going right now . Maybe some other time , huh ?
Huh ?
This world may have blinded me ,
but the Lord has let me see !
You 'll be back . You 'll be back !
I 've been hearing something on the streets the last couple of weeks .
Weird stuff .
Some sort of epidemic of violence is what they 've been saying .
I was talking to one old boy who 's from San Anselmo .
He told me they got some sort of cult up there .
End-of-the-world kind of stuff .
- Well , what are they doing ? - Shooting people , robbing banks .
Same old thing as always .
Whole lot of people gone crazy over some nutty dream they just had .
You wanna know the truth ?
This kind of shit happens at the end of every century .
It does .
It 's just people afraid to face the future , that 's all it is .
FRANK : Hey !
What 's happening ?
I was inside there a while .
All kinds of cardboard boxes , some kind of lab setup .
What do you mean ?
There 's no singing . It 's a tape recorder .
Leave it alone , man .
It ain 't none of my business , ain 't none of yours .
Yeah , but our boy Gilbert 's in there helping them .
I got a job now and I plan on keeping it .
I 'm walking a white line all the time .
I don 't bother nobody . Nobody bothers me .
You better start doing the same .
White line 's in the middle of the road .
That 's the worst place to drive .
I 'll see you later .
Step down . Watch it .
Easy , easy . This way .
All right . Now we cross the road .
It 's dirt here .
( SIRENS WAILING )
Quickly ! Quickly !
( CHATTERING IN SPANISH )
- Go , go , go ! - Come on , this way . This way .
( SIRENS WAILING )
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING , SHOUTING )
Frank !
MAN : We know who you are !
Leave us alone .
We know you .
( INDISTINCT SHOUTING )
God help me !
Help me , Jesus !
" Though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death , I will fear no evil .
" Thy rod and thy staff will ... "
( GROANING )
Jesus !
( BEATING , GROANING CONTINUE )
( TYRES SCREECH , SIREN WAILS )
Come on ! Come on !
Come on in and join the party , man .
You go with him .
Somebody start World War III ?
' Oman 's collection puts passion before fashion .
' Dash and trash are back .
' Out goes glitter and in comes divine excess .
' The fall collection revels in freedom of expression .
' Gay abandon rushes to meet the roaring nineties . '
( CAR HORN BLARES )
( TYRES SCREECH )
SHOPKEEPER : Thank you .
( HUMMING )
What 's your problem ?
I said , what 's your problem ?
How are you today , sir ?
- Okay . How 's it going ? - Fine , thank you .
Thank you , sir .
Here you are , sir . Thank you .
SHOPKEEPER : Hey , buddy .
You gonna pay for that or what ?
Look buddy , I don 't want no hassle today .
Either pay for it or put it back .
Huh !
( DISTORTED VOICE ) ' Sleep ...
' Sleep ...
Can you believe it ? She didn 't even go to Lamaze class .
I told her , " For yourself and for the baby , go ! "
Did Bob make you go to John and Mary Ellen 's last night ?
I was shocked ! She served blue corn tortillas !
So dated ! ( LAUGHING )
I 'm so depressed . I don 't know what to do .
Hey , go for it , man .
That 's easy for you to say , you got the promotion .
Look , it 'll come , all right ? Just don 't worry about it .
TV : ' The feeling is definitely there .
' It 's a new morning in America .
' Fresh . Vital .
' The old cynicism is gone .
' We have faith in our leaders .
' We 're optimistic as to what becomes of it all .
' It really boils down to our ability to accept .
' We don 't need pessimism .
' There are no limits . '
It figures it would be something like this .
Ugh !
Excuse me .
You know , you look like your head fell in the cheese dip back in 1957 .
( GASPS )
You ? You 're okay .
This one ? Real fucking ugly !
You see , I take these glasses off ,
she looks like a regular person , doesn 't she , huh ?
- Put them on ... formaldehyde face ! - That 's enough out of you !
You get out , or I call the cops .
Call the cops ? You know what you need ? You need a Brazilian plastic surgeon .
I 've got one that can see .
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING )
He 's a tall , Caucasian male
that doesn 't appear armed , wearing sunglasses .
I don 't like this one bit .
Not one bit .
( CAR HORN )
That 's like pouring perfume on a pig .
Huh ...
All right , suppose we settle down .
That 's far enough . Where 'd you get those glasses ' ?
The tooth fairy .
I 'll bet .
- We got him . - Nick yourself shaving this morning ?
You look as shitty to us as we do to you .
Impossible !
It would be easier if we don 't have to splatter your brains .
Just take it easy .
Now , you stumbled onto something here .
Maybe we can all benefit from this slight misunderstanding .
Now , let 's go someplace quiet , so we can talk this over .
So , you bastards die just like we do .
( SIREN WAILING )
( TYRES SCREECH )
( WOMAN GASPS ) My goodness !
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING )
I have come here to chew bubble gum and kick ass .
And I 'm all out of bubble gum .
( SCREAMING )
MAN : Near the entrance . Has a shotgun .
White male , thirties . Long hair .
Mama don 't like tattletales .
Wearing sunglasses .
( SIREN WAILING )
( TYRES SCREECH )
( WHIRRING )
' And who are you , little fella ?
' Come to show them where I am .
' Not nice ! '
Drop it !
I said , drop it !
Beat your feet , man .
Take it easy .
I just want a little ride out of here .
Close the door .
Drive .
Not too fast .
They 're gone .
- Just keep driving . - Where am I going ?
- Are you married ? - Yes .
Please , don 't lie to me .
No .
Live alone ?
- Your place . - I 'd rather not do that .
I 'm afraid I must insist .
MAN : Hi , Holly !
Hmm !
Look , I don 't know what you want .
Oh , just quiet . ( CHUCKLES )
Whoo ! It 's like a drug .
Wearing these glasses makes you high , but you come down hard .
Look , things turned out a little sour for me today .
You 're not the only one .
Yeah , well , I 'm sorry , but I needed you to get away .
No !
You have two guns , you 're not sorry .
You 're in charge .
Look , lady , we 're in trouble .
They 're all around us , and we never knew it .
You can only see them with these special glasses .
We 're being controlled by these things .
I don 't know what they are or where they came from , but we gotta stop them .
I 'll do whatever you want , whenever you want ,
just don 't hurt me , please .
Listen to what I 'm saying to you !
Okay .
You 're fighting the forces of evil ...
that none of us can see without sunglasses .
Take a look !
If you want me to look through your sunglasses ,
I 'll look through your sunglasses .
If I don 't see what you see , I 'm going to see it anyway .
You have it your way , huh ?
It 's not my way .
It 's your way .
Don 't fuck with me .
I 'm thirsty .
Go ahead .
Look ...
I 'm sorry I have to be here , huh ?
So , your name 's Holly ?
Holly Thompson .
That 's a pretty name .
So , what do you do ?
Assistant programme director .
Cable 54 .
- A TV station ? - Yes .
They 're sending some kind of signals out of TV sets .
( DOG BARKS )
No , no ...
I 'm all right .
Holly Thompson .
8634 Circle View Drive .
Yes , I 'll hold .
( SIREN WAILING )
( GROANS ) Ugh ...
( HELICOPTER APPROACHES )
( INDISTINCT SHOUTING )
MAN : Frank , I 'm ready when you are !
JOHN : Frank ?
Don 't let nobody see you .
I 've had a rough couple of days .
I don 't want nothing to do with you .
- How many people did you kill ? - Not people .
You crazy son-of-a-bitch .
- I gotta show you something . - No , you ain 't showing me nothing !
I 've got a wife and kids , so leave me alone !
Get out of here !
MAN 1 : Oh , come on , Frank ...
MAN 2 : Hey , move your ass !
( SIREN WAILING )
MAN 1 : I ain 't gonna be picking up nothing !
MAN 2 : Yeah , you wait until I tell the manager !
MAN 1 : Yeah well , then I 'm gonna show him .
MAN 2 : Watch it !
Oh , mo !
No !
( GROANING )
Yo ! One week 's pay .
It 's the best I could do .
Wait !
Hey ! You 'd better find yourself someplace to hide
and keep praying nobody ever finds you .
Try these on .
Look , you crazy mother !
- Put these on . - Hey ! Stay away from me !
I 'm telling you , you dumb son-of-a ...
I 'm trying to save you and your family 's life .
You can 't even save your own !
I 'm giving you a choice .
Either put these on these glasses or start eating that trash can .
- Not this year . - Okay .
All right .
- Okay . - Come on .
Come on .
- I don 't want to fight you . - Come on !
- I don 't want to fight you . Stop it . - No !
Oh , fuck !
- ( GROANS ) Shit ! - Put on the glasses .
Man , I told you I didn 't want to be involved .
You dirty motherfucker !
Take a look .
Put them on .
No !
Fuck it !
( ROARS )
Man , I 'm sorry .
Fuck !
Put the glasses on !
Put them on !
Fuck you !
( GASPING )
Look !
Look at them . They 're everywhere .
Maybe they can see . They 're at 5th and Spring .
Now hold on .
You ain 't the first son-of-a-bitch to wake up out of their dream .
What 's that ?
Brother , life 's a bitch ...
and she 's back in heat .
I want a room .
Ain 't love grand ?
Don 't wear them glasses too long .
It starts to feel like a knife turning in your skull .
How long have they been there ?
Who knows ?
What are they ? Where do they come from ?
- Well , they ain 't from Cleveland . - Look man , I don 't need that kind of shit !
What are we gonna do ?
- We 're gonna wait . - Wait ? Wait for what ?
You know , that really answers my fucking question !
Well , when you get some kind of master plan ,
you let me know , huh ?
We can 't be the only ones who can see .
We gotta find the people who made these .
Yeah , if any of them are still alive .
A long time ago , things were different , man .
My old Daddy took me down to the river ,
kicked my ass , told me about the power and the glory .
I was saved .
He changed when I was little .
He turned mean and started tearing at me .
That 's why I ran away when I was 13 .
He tried to cut me once .
Big old razor blade .
He held it up against my throat .
I said , " Daddy , please ... "
He just kept moving back and forth ...
like he was sawing down a little tree .
Maybe they 've always been with us , those things out there .
Maybe they love it , seeing us hate each other .
Watching us kill each other off .
Feeding on our own cold fucking hearts .
I got news for them .
There 's going to be hell to pay .
' Cause I ain 't Daddy 's little boy no more .
Frank ?
There 's a meeting tonight . Be at this address at 11 o 'clock .
Watch out no one follows you .
The world needs a wake-up call .
We 're going to phone it in .
MAN : Hey , brothers ...
There 's something new going down .
They 're using candyfloss packaging .
It 's like building a park over a toxic waste dump .
Do you see that ? My dad had one like that .
Here 's a list of safe houses .
You 've gotta memorise them and then destroy the paper .
What 's a ' safe house ' ?
- Hey , Frank ! - Hey .
Hey ! Glad you made it .
Oh , you can take your sunglasses off . We 're all human in here .
GILBERT : Memorise these safe houses .
Memorise these safe houses .
Brand-new . Got the first shipment today .
They won 't hurt .
There 's less interference .
Go ahead .
' There is a signal broadcast every second of every day
' through our television sets ,
' even when the set is turned off . '
Hey !
- Any trouble getting here ? - No , we made it fine .
Good . The city is crawling with cops looking for us .
Most of the cops are human .
They 've been told that we 're commies trying to bring down the government .
And some of them are being recruited . The creatures are trading wealth , power .
- People are joining up with them ? - Most of us just sell out right away .
Then all of a sudden we get promoted .
Our bank accounts get bigger , we start buying new houses , cars .
Perfect , isn 't it ?
We 'll do anything to be rich .
TV : ' Look around at the environment we live in .
' Carbon dioxide , fluorocarbons and methane have increased since 1958 .
' Earth is being acclimatised .
' They are turning our atmosphere into their atmosphere . '
What do these things want , and why are they here ?
It 's in their best interests . They 're free-enterprisers .
The earth is just another developing planet ...
their Third World .
' We are like a natural resource to them .
' Deplete the planet , move on to another .
' They want benign indifference . They want us drugged .
' We could be pets . We could be food .
' But all we really are is livestock . '
We need an assault unit .
Someone to hit them hard when the time comes .
You 've got it .
Ever seen their disappearing act ?
Once .
What 's that ?
They all wear these expensive watches .
Turns out they 're really two-way radios . You can listen to their broadcasts .
There 's something else .
Some kind of secret code or hidden control .
They push a button , and all of a sudden ... bang !
They 're gone .
- I 'm trying to figure it out . - All right now , everybody listen up .
Now , we 're obviously not getting to enough people
because look at our numbers tonight .
There should be twice as many of us here .
We 're getting too sloppy . That 's all there is to it .
Now , their detection is becoming more effective .
So , we have to be more careful .
Stay aware of keeping up appearances .
Go to work . Punch your time clocks . Do what 's expected of you .
We 've gotten reckless , and the movement is suffering for it .
Time to stop talking about it , trying to figure out how it happened .
- Now we start spilling some blood . - ALL : Yeah !
- No ! - Wait a minute , wait a minute !
It 's not working !
We don 't stand a chance with a few guns and grenades .
So , what are we supposed to do ?
We bide our time .
We seek out and locate their signal and shut it off . Wake people up !
Now , Dave here works at KRDA .
Now , he claims the signal may be coming from one place .
HOLLY : KRDA is clear .
The transmission is going out clean .
The signal 's coming from somewhere else .
GILBERT : All right , this is the point .
It 's important to find out exactly where this signal 's coming from .
I gotta go talk to someone .
( GILBERT CONTINUES TALKING )
Are you okay ?
Yeah , I 'm okay .
I thought I 'd killed you .
I thought so , too .
I didn 't know .
I 'm so sorry .
Look , I just wanted to ...
Can we just .. ?
Get out !
Get out of here !
Round the back !
( INDISTINCT SHOUTING )
Oh , mo !
- Come on , just get out ! - Go , go , go ...
Keep moving , people .
( GUN SHOTS )
( SCREAMS )
They 're killing everybody .
- I gotta to find her . - Wait a minute . Are you crazy ?
- I gotta see if she 's all right . - Just stay back !
There 's nothing you can do out there .
If I can get this working , I can listen in .
- Frank ... - What ?
- Get set to sweat . - Oh , shit !
( ZOOMING )
- What was that ? - I don 't know .
( CRACKLING )
TANNOY : ' Attention ! Your wristwatch has malfunctioned .
' This entry way is temporary and will disappear ... '
- Get in there ! Move ! - What ?
- We don 't know what 's down there . - Now !
' Eight seconds .
' Seven seconds .
' Six seconds .
' Five seconds .
' Four seconds .
' Three seconds .
' Two seconds .
' One second .
' If you need assistance in finding your destination ,
' bilingual instructions are posted at the end of each corridor . '
- What language is that ? - I don 't know .
Where the hell are we ?
I think we 're under the city .
Maybe some kind of underground base or something .
- There 's got to be a way out . - I just hope nobody saw us drop in .
TANNOY : ' Operation Steel Fist has been a complete success .
' All security stations stand down to operational status .
- ' We have eliminated the terrorists . ' - Okay !
- We got them ! We wiped them out ! - All right !
It 's a win , man . They got to meet the A-Team .
I 'm hearing something .
( APPLAUSE )
Our projections show that by the year 2025 ,
not only America , but the entire planet
will be under the protection and the dominion of this power alliance .
The gains have been substantial ...
both for ourselves and for you , the human power-elite .
You have given us entree to the resources we need
in our on-going quest for multi-dimensional expansion .
And in return , the per-capita income of each of you here tonight has grown .
And this year alone by an average of 39 % .
Isn 't it lovely ?
And I 've just received word that our forces have won a major victory .
The underground terrorist network has been destroyed
here on the West Coast .
We are off crisis alert .
The situation is normal again .
( APPLAUSE )
How you doing , boys ? I didn 't know you 'd been recruited .
Welcome aboard .
You know , you boys really should have dressed for the party
now that you can afford it .
I gotta tell you , I sure am proud to be here .
You seen the whole place ?
I haven 't had a chance to yet .
Come on , I 'll show you around .
You know , I knew me and you had a lot in common
the first time we met .
Hey , waiter !
Thank you , buddy .
Excuse me ...
- Where the hell are we ? - Backstage at the show , boys .
I 'll admit it is a little funky , but it serves its purpose .
How 'd you get here ? Use one of these little portable jobs ?
I know we ain 't supposed to use them except in cases of emergency ,
but they 're so much fun .
Now , you think that 's something , take a look at this .
Go on , take a closer look .
TANNOY : ' Attention , commuters .
' Flight Alpha 7 to Andromeda is now ready for boarding .
' Please step to the transmission platform . '
That 's where they come from .
' All carry-on luggage must be held securely . '
' Thank you for waiting , and we hope you have a pleasant trip . '
I don 't know how it works exactly ,
but it has to do with some sort of gravitational lens deal ,
bending the light or some damn thing ,
but you can move from place to place . World to world if you want to .
You see , the whole thing here works like one big airport .
Boys , let me tell you ,
they got their act together , believe you me .
Evening , boys . Looking sharp .
Wait till you see what I 'm going to show you now .
And here we got the brains of the whole operation .
Master signal goes out from here to the satellite .
We pump it out all over the world .
Pretty fancy , huh ?
I 'm not too familiar with it myself .
Well , boys , that 's as far as we go .
TV PRESENTER : ' ... multi-spectral analysis .
' This will allow space sensors to penetrate natural barriers ... '
Can you get us inside ?
I 've never seen the inside of a TV studio before .
You look like the gentleman to ask .
Well , I guess it wouldn 't be that much of a problem .
You see them boys over there ? Friends of mine .
Hey , fellas , I got a couple of my buddies here .
I thought I 'd give them the grand tour . Think we can go inside ?
Be serious .
You have your authorisation cards ?
Right here .
( GROANING )
Watch the door .
( WAILING )
Soundproof . Where 's that signal ?
It 's up on the roof , I think .
Holly works in there . If she made it , maybe we can find her .
Then we can go to the roof and break that signal .
Wait boys , wait , you 're making a big mistake .
- You made the mistake . - No , you gotta listen to me .
I thought you boys understood . It 's business , that 's all it is .
You still don 't get it , do you , boys ?
There ain 't no countries anymore , no more good guys .
They 're running the whole show .
They own everything , the whole goddamn planet .
They can do whatever they want .
What 's wrong with having it good for a change ?
And they 're gonna let us have it good if we help just them .
They 're gonna leave us alone , let us make some money .
You can have a little taste of that good life , too .
Now , I know you want it . Hell , everybody does .
You 'd do it to your own kind ?
What 's the threat ?
We all sell out every day . Might as well be on the winning team .
See you , boys .
Let 's go .
Is this the two-minute break or the 30-second break ?
I think it 's the 30-second break , but I don 't know .
- I guess we must be running long . - I think so .
TV : ' We are experiencing technical difficulties . '
What the hell is going on ? Come on .
( INDISTINCT SHOUTING )
Oh , my God ! No !
Get down !
- Now what ? - Find out where the hell we are .
- Excuse me ! - Come on , man !
Wait a sec ! Do you know Holly Thompson ?
Come on , man , I mean it !
Holly Thompson . Assistant programme something or other . Where is she ?
TANNOY : ' Security alert .
' Sections Delta and X-Ray report to the fourth floor immediately . '
Who 's Holly ?
Oh , shit !
Well , I hate to interrupt you , folks ,
but could someone please tell me how to get to the roof ?
- Security ! - Uh-uh-uh !
How do I get to the roof ?
There 's an elevator through there . Turn to your left , it 's at the end of the hall .
Thank you very much .
- Well ? - There 's got to be more than one way
to get up there .
Security 950 . Lock the elevators down . They 're on the move .
( SCREAMING )
( GROANING )
( BEEPING )
I hear them on the 19th floor above me .
Got you . We 're on the 21 st . We 'll be waiting for them .
Go !
( GROANING )
Holly !
- Come on ! Come on ! - Hey !
TANNOY : ' Security alert . Intruders in here are heading for the roof .
' Repeat . Intruders ... '
Let 's go !
Frank ! You and Holly clear ?
HOLLY : I 'm clear . Are you ?
Don 't do it .
Don 't interfere . You can 't win .
TANNOY : ' Drop your weapon .
' Stand away from the dish or we will open fire . '
Come inside with me .
' You have ten seconds .
' Nine .
' Eight .
' Seven .
' Six . '
Fuck it !
TV : ' The Oscar winners give a press conference ,
' and how to buy a sail boat ... '
MAN : Gloria , you look like shit . I 'm out of here !
- WOMAN : What happened ? - What 's wrong ?
' All the sex and violence on the screen has gone too far for me
' I 'm fed up with it .
' Film makers like George Romero and John Carpenter
' have to show some restraint . They 're simply ... '
TV : ' You 're filled with lightning .
' When you hit the road , you 're feeling that V6 power as you take control .
' Nothing can stop you now .
' You 're moving on . '
Hey , what 's wrong , baby ?